Fabian Villaseñor

Modesto, CA 95354 (209) 896-6386

Exionite@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/FabianVillasenor

aithub.com/EndingNever

Technical Skills

- Front end experience with React, Javascript, JSX, Angular, Sass, Styled Components, CSS Modules, Authentication, TypeScript, Bootstrap
- Hands on backend experience with Node.js, Node Package Manager, Insomnia, MySQL, jsonwebtoken, custom REST APIs, Fakestore API, OMDb API
- Understanding of Javascript fundamentals such as Data types, Logical Operators, Functions, algorithms, JSON data
- Experience with Github operations in a team

AlphaWorks Project - Tesla Shop https://syntheticdesigner.github.io/tesla-group-project/

Recreation of the Tesla shop, including a small product database. Worked in a team of four, with successful github merges including resolution of conflicts

AlphaWorks Project - Noom Cafe https://endingnever.github.io/NoomCafe/

Collaboration with UX/UI designer Alfonso Martinez for a fake coffee shop. Alfonso Designed, and I built the page in React using Styled Components, complete with a dark mode

AlphaWorks Project - Elden Ring Recreation https://endingnever.github.jo/EldenRing/

Tasked with recreating a static website, I decided to choose the Elden Ring info page. The page is a recreation from scratch using the images and videos from the site, made in React.

Experience

AlphaWorks, Bitwise Industries - React Apprentice

February 2022 - current

- Front End development using React, Styled Components, SASS, and custom CSS
- State, Context, custom hooks, Redux, fetch requests, React Router v5/v6,
- Deployment through Github Pages and Heroku

E&J Gallo - Assoc. Business Systems Analyst

January 2022 - February 2022

• Business system development through ServiceNow

- Experience with Automated Test Frameworks and front-end development for service portal
- Interaction and referencing of different tables, requests, variables, and workflows

Bay Valley Tech - *Intern*

June 2021 - August 2021

- Working within a team, splitting a large project into individually manageable pieces
- Our team built a Youtube Web Player in Angular using the Youtube API
- Handling different Github branches, and merging new features when approved

Bay Valley Tech - Student

December 2020 - September 2021

- Learned the basics of coding with HTML, CSS, and Angular
- Javascript fundamentals through freecodecamp, udemy courses, practicing functions and algorithms,
 and building projects
- Involved Consistent coding, homework, practice, and learning

Doordash - Driver

April 2018 - January 2022

- Self-employed food delivery
- Responsible for all records such as car maintenance, daily miles, expenses for tax purposes
- Clean driving record

Berkshire Hathaway- Licensed Real Estate Agent

August 2019 - November 2020

- Held open houses, following up with prospective clients
- Provide information on available homes, financing

Education

Modesto Junior College

January 2022 - Current

- B.S. Computer Science for transfer
 - o Includes experience with Python, C++, problem solving